DynamoDB is a non-relational database created by AWS.
" 发电机 " 是由 AWS 创建的非关系数据库
For a database, DynamoDB has relatively few knobs and dials for configuration.
对于数据库  DynamoDB 具有相对较少的旋钮和用于配置的 dials
In DynamoDB, you create one table.
在 " 发电机数据库 " 中 创建一个表
With relational databases, we typically think of a database as a collection of tables.
对于关系数据库 我们通常认为数据库是表的集合
But in DynamoDB, one database consists of just one table.
但是在 DynamoDB 中 一个数据库仅包含一个表
The tables you create in DynamoDB have one primary key and an optional sort key.
在 DynamoDB 中创建的表具有一个主键和一个可选排序键
You can create additional indices on the table so that you
您可以在表上创建其他索引 以便
can in effect have multiple primary or sort keys on the table.
实际上 可以在表上具有多个主键或排序键
That's the entire data model for DynamoDB.
这是 DynamoDB 的整个数据模型
It is simple and straightforward,
简单明了
but yet still quite powerful.
但仍然相当强大
The read and write throughput of DynamoDB is measured
度量动态数据库的读写吞吐量
and charged by the number of operations per second.
并按每秒操作数进行充电
You decide how much reading and writing you'll be doing per second,
你决定你每天的阅读量和写作量
and simply set those values on the table or index.
并简单地将这些值设置在表或索引上
You also have options to pay on demand for this usage,
您还可以根据需求付费使用此产品
so that you don't have to pick a number or you can let the capacity auto scale over time.
这样你就不必选择一个数字 也可以让容量自动随时间推移
Again, compared to a traditional relational database,
与传统的关系数据库相比
this is drastically simpler.
这就更简单了
Don't let the simplicity fool you though.
别让简单的事愚弄你
DynamoDB is quite powerful and suitable for many workloads.
发电机非常强大 适合许多工作负载
DynamoDB can scale to handle tens of millions of requests a
可扩展数据库以处理数以千万计的请求
second while automatically scaling up and down as required.
第二个过程是根据需要自动向上和向下扩展
DynamoDB is resilient by default.
缺省情况下  " 发电机 " 具有弹性
AWS runs the service across
AWS 在以下范围内运行服务 :
multiple availability zones and takes care of replicating your data,
多个可用性区域 并注意复制您的数据
so that any single availability zone failure would not impact your DynamoDB tables.
因此 任何单一可用性区域故障都不会影响 DynamoDB 表
This is a big deal.
这是个很大的交易
You don't have to think or worry about configuring DynamoDB to be Multi-AZ.
您不必考虑或担心将 DynamoDB 配置为多 AZ
You also don't have to decide on the cost trade-offs,
你也不用考虑成本权衡
since the cost of running in
因为跑步的成本
multiple availability zones is baked into the base price of the service.
将多个可用性区域烘烤到服务的基本价格中
Speaking of cost, while some of this functionality may sound expensive,
说到成本 虽然其中一些功能可能很昂贵
it is often the case that DynamoDB is actually
DynamoDB 实际上就是
cheaper than a server-based database such as RDS.
比基于服务器的数据库 ( 如 RDS) 更便宜
This is because DynamoDB lets you pay only for what you use,
这是因为 DynamoDB 让你只支付你使用的东西
whereas a dedicated server or servers cost you money 24 hours a day,
而专用服务器或服务器每天花费 24 小时
365 days a year,
一年 365 天
366 days in a leap year.
在闰年里 366 天